Hello, let me see you got the chat going. Hold on start recording. Hello. Am I am I on? Okay. Let me have a look
What's going on YouTube? Okay?
Hi a bit more energy to go. I feel a bit more energy
Just check something out
My life
Yes, I am okay
Okay, 2020. What's up, dude? Are you on the screen? Is it say 2020 on the screen? Do I see it yet? No
Don't I see the the full the bully chest still I think I think I need to pick some stuff like it's like doing a lot of tarot card stuff
Yeah, we do have to card the day of the world. Okay, this is the beginning of a new cycle the end of another cycle
I do have my OBS or
It's called a power chat
set up
So I'm not on my stream, but it's like if you want to send
um power chat you can have your hi Rudy you can have your comment right on the
screen you can request the song it is cult of psyche.com there's like a lot
of stuff set up I don't think it might be I think too much right now but there
you go tell me if that works okay so how are you guys doing yeah um the chat
Oh my gosh. Yeah, I don't have that. That's my kid. That's my kid. I am on the tripod today. I need to do my
See, I need to do a few things. I figure out the green screen on this one. Let me fix this tripod, put this on Facebook or not.
Okay. Yeah, I did have a shower today. There we go.
I'm not too close.
I don't think we'll see.
But yeah, so this is kind of a test stream.
We are working through some stuff.
Forwarding is currently broken.
Let me confirm the actual page itself works.
OK, yeah.
So it'll be working, guys.
It'll be working.
Might go while we're working on it. I might go over to my stream yard
But wow, there's a lot of cool stuff on this stream. I mean when the chat really gets going that'll be cool
Okay, it says hey psyche biscuit vibes
Is that a real person biscuit vibes?
How's that? Oh, so I'm going to pretend that it's just a real chat. That'd be so much fun
He knows what?
Hard to pull exactly. I love this chat. It's a great chat
Yeah, so the power chat will be really cool when it works. It was a clock on top. There's a morning cancer season
It's putting some cool stuff on the screen
I might have to move that because it's like a queen right on my face. I suck. Oh, you stuck
Okay, everyone go check out black RG on QE farms everybody
Check out black RG on QE farms
If you want to tell me I suck you have to actually pay for the TTS and put that in there because I'll just be hiding you
Okay, he retracted it well, it's not see Pokemon is see Pukini on or something like that
Well, if it's not him. He has your twin dog and you know looks like you sound so I mean it's a really relevant
What was really relevant is what you did
Which is like what you had a blind guy rub beasties into his space?
And you like you even have me feel bad for Tony you have Tony microwave his phone and you know the drink is toilet water
Okay, it doesn't matter if you're him or not, RG, the thing is, it's like, are you gonna
change your ways?
I'm just wondering, if someone thought I was like, you know, Steve Birmingham or something
in Nevada, I would just say, yeah, I'm him because they'd be wrong.
I wouldn't even protest it.
I don't understand.
Why do you even care?
If I'm doxing you incorrectly, then who cares?
But if I'm gonna try to dox you, I'm just like staying publicly available information.
Here we go.
Time for shadow work, right?
Okay
But anyway, I'm so much worse or a person than you are
What I do to anybody I'm worse of a person. What does that mean though?
Have I like bully people have I like, you know, you did a whole thing where you dox beat is like aunt and her phone numbers
Or her dress was streaming on your thing
I mean, then you're like a bully and you're absolute bully to people, but then you like play the nice guy, you know
But if you want to like, um, insult me again, you have to pay for the TTS, um, yeah, hold
on.
They don't have the panel up tonight, but you would have been come on the panel anyway.
Okay, works on HGTV, Brooklyn, HGTPS, no SS, okay, well, try the link guys, try the link.
Are you getting a link?
All this work in a channel is dead.
But how about I do like, you know, I was timing up a little bit
You're dead RG. I mean RG if the handle is dead, I'd be dead wouldn't I should try getting a job
Well, you should try
Doing something other than just trolling so go away. I'll see you tomorrow. Oh
Everything's gone. Oh
It's gone. Why are you tracking messages because you don't you're like, I'm I didn't say anything to him
But there we go
I mean, I'm in a little backup channel. I don't understand why people are just like you just can't leave me alone
Let's be like obsessed with me
Some people right? I mean, geez
All I'm doing is trying something new. I mean, it's like I can't even you know
Everyone has to be like, you know judged by some some little oh my gosh my nails were dirty
And maybe on several occasions, but if what it's like that defines me as a human being
It's like, no, that's not bad enough. So it has to be now has to be shit in his nails because you know Barry said that once it must be like something like
That that work. No, it's like doesn't even work. That doesn't work. I don't really don't care
I'm not I'm desensitized that word but some people aren't they're gonna be like, oh
You're gonna be like, oh, that's a that's gross
You know, even though it's not true and it's just fabricated. It's just like, you know
Smearing by association. I mean, it's like not very creative. Christine like your face. You're working in some material or your material needs some work
Oh my god, okay. Well, was this a success? I don't know
I mean, it's like we're someone's gonna need to eventually test out the TTS and have the message right on the screen
There we go
We are having a tower moment. Oh my gosh. I mean all this is happening at once, okay, but let me see what the
Robot is telling me before I go
It might come back on the on the uh, I might make it might come back on the
Okay, hold on. Okay. I need to do so. I need I guess I need to fix some stuff. Okay, but
Eventually this will work, but I'm gonna come back on my
Stream yard
And we have a chat there, okay
We need more work. Hi, babe. Okay, let's see. I'm gonna stop recording and I'll be back on my stream yard